seocorporation.net 2017-06-24

# SEO Corporation privacy policy

#### What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you place an order.   
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

#### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

To process transactions  
Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

#### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order.  
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to?keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be kept on file for more than 60 days.

#### Do we use cookies?

We do not use cookies.

#### Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. uses.

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.  
Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. 

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. 

Website: [www.seocorporation.net](http://www.seocorporation.net/)  
Email ID: [info@seocorporation.net](mailto:info@seocorporation.net)
